Key Modules: Fundamentals of computer programming, data structures, algorithms, numerical methods, statistics, design patterns, human-computer interaction, computer graphics, information visualization, database.

Proven ability to leverage full-stack knowledge and experience to build interactive and user-centered website designs to scale. Extensive expertise in large system architecture development and administration, as well as network design and configuration.

Areas of Expertise

- ♦ Node.
- ♦ SQL
- ♦ JSON
- ♦ HTML

- ◆ CSS (Cascading Style Sheet)
- ◆ Front-End Development
- ♦ Back-End Development
- ♦ Software Testing

- ♦ Software Development
- ♦ JavaScript
- ♦ Microsoft Office Suite
- ♦ Relationship Building

Education

Warren Woods Tower High School 2007-2012 Michigan State University , Lansing, MI Graduate Student – Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp

January, 2023

- Contributed software engineering expertise in the development of products through the software lifecycle, from requirements definition through successful deployment.
- Worked on the multiple software projects simultaneously and participated in the whole software development process from design to implementation and delivery.
- Developed expertise in creating web based applications while determining choices that maximize increased customer satisfaction and loyalty.

Experience Highlights

- Conduct troubleshooting to resolve IT-related and application issues
- Provide clients with information on available upgrades and troubleshoot computer-related problems for internal and external clients
- Diagnosed and resolved a range of software, hardware, and connectivity issues
- Responded to client account questions, including billing and field service requests.
- Performed remote troubleshooting using diagnostic techniques and relevant questions.

FedEx Office, Ann Arbor, MI Lead Retail Consultant

2019 – 2021

Provided pricing information and recommended appropriate FedEx Office products and services while taking customer orders. Operated printing, binding, and other production-related equipment. Managed, monitored, and facilitated all production processes. Leveraged exceptional consultative skills to anticipate needs, suggested alternatives, and provided solutions to colleagues and customers. Completed required financial paperwork and supported with financial reporting including daily sales, close-outs, and bank deposits.

- Delivered a positive customer experience to all customers.
- Shouldered all responsibilities of store as a lead consultant, including opening and closing the store.
- Demonstrated consultative behaviour to ensure a courteous and knowledgeable service is delivered to all customers.

Airbnb, Houston, TX 2021 - Present

Remote Host

Provide guests with exceptional hospitality and customer service. Manage calendars and schedule regular cleanings for guests. Resolve issues in timely manner while maintaining high standard of professionalism. Perform regular pricing evaluations and maintain financial records.

Consistently booked months throughout the year.